I'm sorry. Is this chair free?
Yeah, um... sure.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
-  Ah, whoo!
And please don't give her any
apple juice before bedtime.
Apple juice, yes, yes.
Like the other night.
Yeah, but no apple juice.
Yeah, it's too much sugar.
Okay, no.
- Hi-hi.
- Hi, Ma.
- Ciao.
...cooking class.
Today we made ravioli
with um,
I think there were bits of
sausages inside it.
Well, you should come
to the cooking class with us
maybe tomorrow,
because I believe that tomorrow
they're making the gnocchi.
The ravioli that they tried to
teach--
-  Oh, right.
I'm sorry to bother you during
this very lovely dinner.
I just want to say two things.
I hope we didn't wake you up,
because the noise you heard last
night, the banging on the door,
- Very quickly, that was me.
- We couldn't find our way,
so we were very late here.
Ah-ah, sorry for that.
Ah, we don't know each other.
That's the way it goes on holidays.
But uh, you know, I want to meet
you people,
because you look all so nice
and beautiful.
And uh, I want to toast to you,
guys. To Italy, of course.
To the food, of course.
And to love.
Too love, salute!
Like a bunny... for kids?
Nah? Okay, well. Ciao.
Ciao.
It goes up and down,
and up and down--
It's so hot,
yeah. But you do it--
Hi!
This is my husband, Bjørn.
Patrick, nice to meet you.
We met at the Villa?
-  Hi.
- Hi. Karin.
Sorry, I forgot to introduce
myself. I'm Louise--
-  Hello.
- and this is Agnes.
And what's your name?
Abel has difficulties speaking.
So, if he feels some sort
of pressure
he can get
a little insecure.
-  Ahh.
- But there's no pressure at all.
And who is this?
Ninus.
Ninus?
Agnes just lost it,
so Bjørn went to find it.
You went to find the rabbit?
Yes.
That's very heroic of you.
Thank you.
No, no. I'm serious... respect.
Well, thanks.
You're very welcome.
So, did you guys have lunch yet?
By the way,
where are you guys from?
Holland,
the southern part.
Yeah, countryside,
it's a beautiful area.
Wow, I would just love to move
outside the city
and be close to nature and all--
yeah.
Well, you should come and visit us.
- That would be great--
-  Lasagna Vegeteriana.
-  Prego.
- Ci , Vegetarian?
-  Vegetarian.
- Yes, thank you.
Tagliatelle ai funghi.
- Ci, grazia.
E pizza margherita.
So, you're a vegetarian?
Yeah, I eat fish, but yes,
I'm a vegetarian.
That's so good.
We could all learn from you.
Yeah, good for the environment, really.
Well... thank you--
E peposo.
Oh, Grazie mille .
Oh, I'm starving.
- It looks good.
-  Looks great.
Wow.
Well, I actually think that
Dutch and Danish people
are very similar.
Yeah, so we're the same.
Well, in many ways I think so, actually.
It's uh, the same humor,
the same um, the same um...
same culture.
Yeah, at least we have more in
common with people from Holland,
than with the Swedish people.
I's so glad you say that.
- Yeah?
Really. No, I had
a Swedish colleague
when I worked for the Médecins
Sans Frontières.
You're a doctor?
Yeah.
No, really. He was the most
boring and political correct man
I've ever met in my entire life.
-  Really.
...you know saying weird
stuff!
Like once we were in Greece,
I was going with the cheering.
I was going... "Kalimera!"
Good morning!
"Dear Louise, Bjørn and Agnes.
How are you?
We were just talking
the other day
how nice it was spending time
with you this summer.
And even though
it's been a while,
we would love to invite you
to come to visit us.
- What do you say?"
"A weekend
in the Dutch countryside.
Food, wine and long walks.
And, oh, by the way, Abel keeps
mentioning Agnes. So funny.
He really misses her.
All the best
from Abel, Patrick and Karin."
Yeah, you made it!
Finally, yes.
Yes, yes!
-  Hi.
So nice
to see you again.
Hey, man.
What a beautiful place.
Thank you.
Oh no, you can leave
them on. Or take them off.
Leave them on.
Or take them off.
Leaving 'em on, taking 'em off,
whatever you want.
- Thank you.
- Give me your coat.
Sorry for the mess.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's gonna get much worse. Come
on!
So, come in.
Wow, very comfortable.
Yeah, that's the way we like it.
Oh, and we brought you something.
Oh!
It's a little souvenir
from Denmark.
It's Louise who bought
it, so...
Thank you.
Uh, where's Abel?
- Uh, downstairs maybe?
- Oh.
He's been cooking all day.
He's making Wild Boar.
Come on.
This is your room.
- Wow.
- Ah, that's wonderful.
-  Bjørn?
- Yes.
- You want a beer?
-  Yeah.
I want to show you my pool.
- You have a pool?
-  Uh-huh.
Hi Abel.
Look, Agnes, we made you a
little bed.
-  Do you like it?
- Yes, she likes it.
I forgot the presents.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's fine.
Wow... it's coffee cups.
That's sweet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And... a mermaid?
Yes, it's something that I think
represents Denmark very well.
- It's The Little Mermaid.
- Yeah.
I know it.
I've heard it's quite small
and disappointing.
Well, actually there are some
anecdotes about it
that are really nice.
Oh yeah, you know what is also
nice?
- Louise...
- Hmm?
This is for you.
Oh, no-no, that's fine--
I insist.
- I insist.
No-no,
I'll wait till--
- It's my favorite part.
- Okay.
It's delicious. It's crispy and
soft at the same time.
- Yes.
Yeah.
- Hmm.
- It's good, right?
Very good.
Oh, hi Abel.
But it is really lucky we've got
the GPS,
because otherwise we'd have got
lost like 20 times
I had it under control.
No, [laughing] the GPS had.
- I had.
It's frightening sometimes,
how we lose our ability to find
our way through life.
Because we hand over the
responsibility to technology.
That is so true.
I mean, people nowadays don't
have a clue how to read a map.
I must admit that driving in a
car like that,
with GPS and all these
modern things, you--
I-I want to turn it off sometimes.
And, as you were saying,
Patrick--
Is he all right?
No, no, he's fine. He's fine.
He'll fall asleep in a minute.
He just does this sometimes.
It's part of his disease.
Oh yeah, what is that?
Abel has what you call
"congenital aglossia".
Meaning basically, he's born
without a tongue.
Or... a much smaller tongue than
you and me.
But is he in pain?
Oh no, no pain.
He just has a hard time
making himself understandable.
Oh no, I understand everything
he says.
Excuse me
for just one second.
Um, Abel, do you think you could
move away?
Uh, because Agnes really wants
to try it.
Uh, excuse me?
Agnes really wants
to try the slide.
And do you think
it is possible
to ask Abel to move away
just for one second?
So sorry about this.
No, it's okay, it's nothing.
Patrick, it's all right.
He doesn't have to.
No, he wants to say
"I apologize".
Yeah,
he really wants to.
Sorry.
- I must have the recipe.
- It's good, right?
It reminds me
of what we call a Mazarin?
A Mazarin tart...
a Danish thing.
Come here.
Hey, am I interrupting?
No-no, of course not.
Well Patrick and I would like to
invite you to dinner tonight.
Oh, that's so nice of you.
Yeah, there's a nice restaurant
with great local food
just up the road.
And we wouldn't want you
to miss the opportunity
while you're here.
That sounds good.
Great.
Yes, perfect timing.
He doesn't speak
any English.
And who is Muhajid?
He's the babysitter.
- The babysitter?
-  Yeah.
But the kids are going as well, right?
No, tonight is without kids.
Didn't I tell you that?
Muhajid is so very good
with children.
The whole neighborhood uses him
and not only because he's cheap.
Let's go!
Come on, let's move.
Patrick, are we at the
restaurant soon?
We'll be there in a minute.
Uh, What is the "stamppot"?
Oh, that's great. It's the house
specialty... you should try it,
- Okay
- It's good.
Yeah, and the "boerenkool"?
Boerenkool. Oh, that's also
stamppot, you'll love it.
It's delicious, they make it
very well here.
And what is stamppot?
Stamppot? Oh, that's typical
Dutch. Very traditional.
Like potatoes and vegetables,
you stamp it all together.
Steef! Let me take care of you
guys. Okay?
Yeah, fine with me.
And remember, I'm a vegetarian.
I'm sorry?
Yes, I don't eat meat.
Oh, yes, yes. So good
for the environment, yes.
But you eat fish, right?
Yes.
So you're not a vegetarian,
you're a pescatarian.
Yes.
Yes, Steef?
Hmm?
And fish is not meat?
Of course, um, but it's better
for the environment.
And the way
the fishing industry works
and how we treat the oceans
is not affecting the climate?
Well, I would like
to propose a toast--
- Okay.
- For uh,
- good times.
- For good times.
- We say proost.
- Proost.
-  Proost.
Well,
I just hate this...
This, um, this team building
bullshit, you know.
♪ Was just in time replaced
By the magic appearance ♪
Of a new day while ♪
♪ A melancholic reno was
crawling on his back just in ♪
♪ Front of
The supermarket doorway ♪
♪ On a cold summer night as we
stood on the corner ♪
♪ As a man passed by and asked
us what we were doing ♪
What we need ♪
♪ As he pointed
His big fat finger ♪
♪ To the people hangin' round ♪
♪ At the corner
Of the other side of street ♪
Oh well ♪
♪ Doin' nothing,
just hanging around... ♪
just hanging around ♪
♪ His head all busted lookin'
just a little too wise child ♪
I just can't wait ♪
For Saturday night ♪
Saturday night ♪
Saturday night. ♪
Wow.
Someone had
a really good time tonight.
You want us to chip in?
Oh, thanks man.
So the dinner is on us?
Oh, that's so kind.
Thanks, man, thanks.
Ah.
Patrick, can you turn down the
music a bit?
Patrick, the music, can you turn
it down--
I love this song.
This is a great song!
Turn down the fucking music.
Listen to it!
I'm so sorry, he's just so
drunk. I'm truly sorry. Okay?
I truly apologize,
I'm so sorry.
And ya!
- Patrick!
- Just a little bit, please?
Just a little bit down.
-  Okay, a little bit.
- Yeah!
Yeah. Thank you.
Bjørn, Bjorn, Bjørn, Bjorn!
Bjørn.
We had
some really lovely days here.
- Huh?
-  What's going on?
Well, uh,
we have a situation here.
Someone left
without saying goodbye.
No, as I was just trying
to tell Patrick,
we had some really lovely days.
And then I ask again, why are
you leaving--
We had some good days,
it's just um...
there's just some things that...
that make us believe that
it's best that we go home.
What are those things?
I want to know.
- It's um, many things.
- Such as?
It's just, um... such as...
Such as the bed for instance.
It's really small, and uh,
and Agnes doesn't want to sleep
on the floor,
so she comes in at night.
Okay, so
with all of your respect...
First of all, I'm a vegetarian.
But all you've been doing since
we got here was serving meat.
But we have all sorts of food.
You can have a hagelslag
sandwich right now.
I can make it for you.
No, thank you.
And last night
at that restaurant or...
roadhouse or whatever that place
was, it was...
it was very uncomfortable
to drive.
And the music was so loud.
And you were drinking
and driving.
And the way you were touching
each other in front of us
that just made me so
uncomfortable, I'm really sorry.
But it just um... so many things
have felt so wrong.
I'm really sorry,
but it's just how it is.
I'm in shock.
Can-can I say something?
Uh, first of all... Louise.
I am so sorry that we forgot
that you were a vegetarian.
And if there are things
you don't eat,
you just could have told us.
Right?
And our house is not huge,
so we cannot offer you
a big luxury room
and a king-size bed, Bjørn.
I'm sorry.
And I am truly sorry that Agnes
doesn't feel comfortable
staying in Abel's room. But we
thought it was only natural.
I mean, if you only knew how
much Abel was looking forward to
sharing his toys
in his room with Agnes.
And the roadhouse,
as you call it...
the hugging and the dancing.
We were just having a fun
evening. Guys, come on.
I mean, dancing
and kissing the one you love.
What's the problem?
To me, it's crossing the line
when you pick up my daughter
at night.
And then you take her
into your bed,
where you slept next to her, naked.
Yeah but, where were you?
Louise,
I mean, Agnes kept calling?
She was crying.
Where were you?
First of all there's nothing we
can do now to change the way
you have felt
during these past few days.
And it truly breaks my heart
to hear
that you haven't enjoyed
your stay.
It makes me wonder
if maybe I've failed as a host.
No one is forcing you to stay.
But I really hope you do, 'cause
today is gonna be a great day.
I promise you, today,
it's gonna be great.
It's this scissor. It doesn't
cut anything, it's so dull.
This is okay
if I turn on the radio?
Yeah, of course.
You can turn it up if you like.
So, what kind of music
do you like?
Ah, well...
yeah, I listen to,
you know, all kinds.
Like uh... like pop
and rock and, uh...
yeah, basically all kinds
you know.
- And you?
- Me too.
Pop, rock... funk.
Hmm.
I like music that I can sing
along to. I like singing.
- Yeah, singing is good.
- Yeah.
Actually, there's a lot
of great Dutch music.
You want me
to play you some?
Yeah yeah, please. I'd really
like to hear some.
- You sure?
- Yeah, really.
This is called "It Never Ends".
And who is it?
Trijntje Oosterhuis.
I think,
this is how an angel sounds.
I really want to apologize
for my behavior last night.
I'm sorry I made you feel
so uncomfortable.
No, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
You know, sometimes I have
this thing, right here.
And it's so powerful and wild.
And I like it.
That's the weird part.
I really like it.
You understand?
Yeah.
You do?
Totally.
Normally, I just uh...
just try to hold it down or...
keep it in chains.
Why?
I don't know why.
Too many rules, I guess...
- It's um--
- It's what?
It's clau--
Yeah, I don't know,
It's... claustrophobic,
you know?
It's like I become this person
I don't want to be.
Who is that person?
I don't know. It's... some guy.
Some normal guy who gets up
in the morning and...
... takes his daughter
to school and... goes to work.
Play a little squash
once a week.
Have dinner with people
I don't even like.
And I'm so tired
of smiling all the time.
Come.
Come, I want
to show you something.
- It's fantastic.
- This is the life, huh?
Louise, thank you so much
for helping out in the garden.
Oh, you're very welcome.
Um, they want to show a dance.
Oh, that's so nice. Maybe when
we have coffee.
Agnes, can you set the table, please?
Ah!
Patrick, maybe you could take a
look at her finger?
Sure.
It's good that we have a doctor
in the house.
I'm not a doctor.
But didn't you say
you were a doctor?
Did I? Oh, I lied.
- You lied?
-  Yeah.
Sometimes I get a little
insecure when I meet new people.
He just wanted to make a good impression.
What do you work with then?
- I don't work.
- No?
No, I'm unemployed.
I've never worked,
I don't believe in working.
Uh.
Oh, that's wrong. It's the other
way around.
Okay?
Sorry.
-  Yes.
- No, ow! Okay.
Yeah, I got this, thank you.
Who needs a doctor, right?
Bread? Yes.
You know, it's a shame
that Holland is not really
being recognized
as a producer of fine
and high quality cheese
like Italy or France
for example.
Oh, here.
I mean, we are a cheese nation.
We export more cheese than any
other country in the world,
besides Germany, of course.
But I sometimes feel...
that Dutch cheese is not getting
the respect it deserves.
Everyone should come with Bjørn
and me to the market
and try some of Johan's cheese.
Then they will give Dutch cheese
the respect it deserves.
Johan said it himself.
Forget Stilton,
forget Gorgonzola.
Dutch cheese, Dutch cheese
is the number one, right?
- Bjørn.
- Hmm?
The cheese at the market,
it was good, right?
- It was fantastic.
- It was number one.
- Johan said it himself, cheers!
- Cheers.
Stop telling my daughter what
to do.
It's not up to you to tell
my daughter what to do, okay?
Okay, relax. I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
-  Okay?
One, two, three, four.
It's okay.
They're both really good.
Yes, but he has no rhythm.
And he's messing up the routine.
No, but they are just kids.
Yes, but if he wants to reach
his potential,
he has to concentrate,
right? Right.
Okay, one more time.
No, she has to stay
because it's a duet.
No,
she doesn't want to.
No, she has to stay.
She doesn't want to dance anymore.
Uh, what's the problem?
You cannot... he's only a child
for Christ's sake.
I mean, what the hell is wrong
with you?
Can't you see he's crying?
He's in pain?
You can't talk to him that way.
What is wrong with you?
Oh my god, what's wrong?
Because we do things
differently?
This is not about doing things differently.
It's not about that.
No! This is about doing
what is right.
This is really...
to do what is right for you.
Like showing your son some love
when he is crying
instead of shouting
at him.
Yeah, and Patrick,
what the fuck?
Why can't you just
let him dance?
Oh, that wasn't dancing.
Yeah, but you threw a cup
at him!
Sorry, but I can't listen to you
talk to him that way.
You threw a cup at the wall!
Okay, stop this please.
Please stop it.
Bjørn, can you please
take her inside?
I don't want her to see me
like this.
Hello?
Hello!?
Louise?
Louise!?
Agnes!?
Agnes!
Hey Bjørn.
Thanks for the call.
I'm glad you agreed
to meet us up on the road.
Thanks for helping us out.
It's very nice of you.
Of course, hmm.
Get in the car.
Please don't hurt
us. Please don't hurt my family.
We just want to go home.
Hey, it's okay. Relax.
As long as you do as we say,
it's gonna be fine.
Do you know when we
will be back at the house?
It won't be long now.
Is Abel alone
at the house?
No, Muhajid is looking
after him.
He was up early anyway, so...
Are we there soon?
Be quiet.
Excuse me?
Will you be quiet, please?
Can you tell us when
we'll be back at the house?
Shhhhhh.
We're going
to your house, right?
Now you have to tell us
what's going on--
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
- Don't talk to my family like--
Louise, please let go of her.
Louise...
You will let go, yes.
- No.
-  You will, you will.
Why are you doing this?
Because you let me.
Take off your clothes.